So I went on Twitter yesterday. I bet you can tell where this is going.
I don't really want to live on this planet anymore. Back in ancient times like in...
2007, when Twitter was created, you could do nothing about it. But today we can!
Thanks to the power of VR we can leave this place, and I have decided to move into Minecraft VR permanently.
It's a big decision, but it had to be made.
I said goodbye to my cactus, and my crayfish balloon, and started the program.
Ah...
Already feel at home.
"But Killian if you move into Minecraft VR, won't you starve to death???? I find logical errors in YouTube videos!!!!"
No, I won't starve. You see, one day in Minecraft is 20 minutes in real life, and I've eaten one of
those fish food pellets that lasts two weeks.
Which means I don't have to eat anything for two and a half years!
In the game on the other hand...A big problem with Minecraft VR is that if you die here you die in real life.
That seems like a pretty big deal. Why haven't I heard about it?
Well,
Someone took Microsoft to court, and the tech giant won the case,
Because they pointed out they could not be sued because anyone who tried to sue them would be dead.
That's why my current priority is to secure the physiological needs to survive.
I'll focus on shelter first by finding a village. Not gonna live alone in the forest.
That's a crazy person decision. As opposed to a sane person decision, like moving into Minecraft.
I found one!
Hello villager. What is the name of this village?
It's called "haww."
Okay, then from now on I am "haww"-ish. My first morning as a "haww" citizen.
I need to build a house similar to theirs, so they don't stone me for ruining the village aesthetics.
All I need is wood and stone.
If I had emeralds...dooby, dooby, dooby dooby dooby dooby dooby, dumb...
This is...
Nice.
This is all it's going to be by the way, just a simple video of me relaxing in Minecraft VR.
If you were hoping for an overly complex plot with lots of layers and storylines, you've come to the wrong place.
Look at that, I finished the house. Beautiful view, and a cozy second floor.
Now we need to focus on the other two needs.
Water is easy. I have it right over there!
Tastes...exactly like I expected pixelated water to taste.
Now I need to create my farm for food!
Wheat for bread, and, of course, liquid bread....
Potatoes, and then I can mix that with wheat soil to create chips.
And beetroot so I can make...
Some delicious borscht.
Do I have anything else I can grow?
CARROTS! I HATE CARROTS! And I won't tell you why!
I have secured all the basic needs.
Now I move on to the second level: security. In layman's terms, I gotta get a job.
No offence to unemployed people, they make up 94% of my audience.
But in pre-electric times, if you didn't have a job, they threw you out of the village
Hmm. What am I qualified for?
"Write jokes on the Internet."
It's not gonna help me here.
If an EMP destroys all electricity, be sure to leave out food for starving youtubers.
Doesn't seem to be any police around...I could cook...
No, Mojang said they won't add hydrochloric acid. Until the next patch.
I don't like the sun enough to farm, and I can't become a butcher because I feel bad for
fictional animals, as opposed to real animals.
I need a job
similar to my previous one, where I tell people my opinions, and no one dares to oppose me. Wait,
yes, of course. I should become a cleric!
I'll just stand in front of everyone, and call them terrible people! I'll go talk to the previous cleric.
He did not want to leave his job...
Villagers!
Your previous cleric ran off with an exotic dancer. I am your cleric now!
No, I am not covered in blood. This is from all the borscht I eat! "But Kilian how does a cleric make money?"
Medieval priests had this trick they called faith
Blackmail. Hey
I saw you eat bread on the specific day, we aren't allowed to eat bread. Give me emeralds
or go straight to the nether! Hey cartographer! Some of your maps aren't completely accurate! Give me emeralds
or go straight to the nether! Everyone, give me emeralds
or you're all going to the nether! It carried on like that. Time moved quickly.
Metaphorically on top of time moving quickly...
You know what I mean! I've lived here for a year. Starting to consider this place my home.
I do miss stuff from the real world though a cold glass of soda
the smell of freshly cut grass
But most of all I miss I missed that video of a lazy eyed cat who wants chips
He tries to dig through the bag
But but he's not allowed to eat them if I had all of those things. This would be a paradise
Maybe I don't have to finish the security step and can move on to love and belonging
Let's go make a friend. Hello
Okay, run away. Hi there. I don't think you're allowed to say that word. Good day
That's rough buddy. I should get going
I could really use an icebreaker to start conversations as a Clara can only have this red stove
wait a
Rate we're being invaded. My flock is being massacred precisely the moment
I've made three harps of a friend. I need to make weapons but Brando because I skipped that step
I have all these diamonds I can learn how to but I need more time. I only know how to use redstone wait
time
Redstone. Oh
My Nolan I have to build minecraft VR in Minecraft VR
I have to go one layer deeper where time is slower the autumn it is it's gonna be so confusing and complex
The one thing I didn't what happen. Bye for now. I'll be right back
I'm awake and it's cold water. Oh, no, it should be ice when it's this freezing
You see on the second tip of your level on virtual reality games box usually manifest themselves as bugs
But because minecraft is made in Java it manifests itself as coffee
But because minecraft doesn't have coffee and coffees 90% water bugs manifest themselves as water
The point is every day the second I finish the sentence
Okay, so it's just normal water. Okay. I need to find out how to make weapons using diamonds
But first I need to get down from here. I only see one option. I'll have to jump down into water
But this is a huge risk, if here the VR arched a torch take my way down
But I'm on my own and I really really need to get back to what this video was previously about, right?
I can't do it. Hah and no slot. I have hidden traumas about our slots
Geronimo
I
Survived and I feel like I've become so connected to the VR that it feels like I'm playing normal minecraft
What's a cool in-universe explanation for my computer not being able to handle amplified VR?
Let's go hunt some diamonds. I've searched for maybe two weeks, but it's felt like two hours
It's probably been two hours and I can't find any diamonds only coal and redstone. Of course
Of course on this level time moves faster
That's why the mountains are so tall and the diamonds would have turned back into coal
I need to pick a new weapon a bow because that would be really cool in VR for that
I need string and that's dropped by spiders. Here's a spider cave next to our carrot patch
Oh, I should take a look in what in the nether are those things?
Okay, slowly walk away. I'm minding my own business. Hi there. Ah, the creatures are weird
Wait, of course, it's so logical not only this time moved faster here minecraft salsa cubicle
So it moves four times faster and the manifestations of spiders would have evolved into impossible minecraft shapes
I can't defeat these things because I don't have any weapons. I'll have to weigh them out
We need to go deeper. I need to create Minecraft er in Minecraft er in Minecraft er time
There will be way further ahead and these spiders would be long gone and then I can collect their string. This is so complex
I didn't want to be this complex. Goodnight. I'm awake again. I need to get string hot. Damn
Everything is breaking down either the minecraft engine can't handle all this information or my brain is melting
Both things are equally terrifying I should see if I can buy some string in this village
Hello, it's me. Leo DiCaprio. You are currently in Minecraft VR minecraft VR
I'm here to rescue you, but I need to find some string you saw some east of here. Thank you
I'll head there right now. No
Ocelots. I can't do this but I have to get string my only way a supports all through the nether you see one step in
The nether is eight steps in the real world
But because we are three levels - one step is actually 24 steps, which would mean right here
Wait, where am I? Ah?
Back in New York, I must have left the game. I can't possibly still be in the game, right?
I should spin a coin to find out wait. We live in a cashless society. Now. I am definitely back in the real world
Look, there's the Chrysler Building. I need to find a slice of pizza
It's way better than Neapolitan pizza because I've been in New York in my entire life. Hey by San Jose you doin
Ah the New York llamas. It's like meeting Frank Sinatra. Thank ninja turtles I left minecraft
I'm gonna miss whatever it was
I did back there
But it's time to get back to my real job as a New York plumber who only helps people that don't like carrots
Hello, New York library
Hello. Bear. Wait a minute. Something's very wrong. 1 2 3 4 5 is
the Bank of America Tower is
287 meters tall where literally everyone in the universe knows it's always been
287 point nine meters tall. Wait a minute. I've never been to New York in my entire life
I'm still in Minecraft and it's collapsing. I have to get out of here
I died, but I'm alive. I know this place
This is the dev room here is where I will spend the rest of eternity
Unless I come to a big realization about myself and develop as a character
But that's not gonna happen unless-unless I have dramatic music by Hans Zimmer in the background to dialog over
But I can't really afford him not within my budget
maybe
something that sounds similar but is copyright free I have lived here for what feels like
27 seconds, but it could be more as I am
Dialoguing it's only me this endless void and a chest that I dare not open
For I know what's in the chest. It's the sweet stats made me want to move to Minecraft
I have to read it to reach
self-actualization
She was mauled to death and it's my fault
I bought her perfume, even though it had a warning label that said it's smell could enrage ocelots
I have to accept that I killed my wife
Hey, I'm back. Well, that was a fun gameplay session, but I'm so hungry though
I could really go for some borscht then. Maybe I can come back and play some more minecraft
I'm sorry this took so long to make I have a lot of problems with it
Technical and writing problems talked a bit about it on my discord at discord.gg/kilian
or Link in top comments